const firstSiskuQuizzes = [
	{
		id:1,
		status:'published',
		name:'Mathematics Quiz #1',
		category: 'mathematics',
		author: 'Jhon Doe',
		authorUsername: 'jhondoe',
		description: 'A quiz to show your basic mathematics skills.',
		scores: [],
		averageScore: null,
		bestScoreBy: [],
		bestScore: null,
		createdOn: '07/01/2019 - 12:00',
		lastModification: '07/01/2019 - 12:01',
		questions:[
			{
				question:'36 + 78 = __?',
				answers:['114','34','52','11'],
				rightAnswer:0
			},
			{
				question:'50 - 25 = __?',
				answers:['10','25','37','84'],
				rightAnswer:1
			},
			{
				question:'10 * 4 = __?',
				answers:['14','50','40','44'],
				rightAnswer:2
			},
			{
				question:'10 / 10 = __?',
				answers:['100','1','23','1'],
				rightAnswer:3
			},
			{
				question:'26 + 90 = __?',
				answers:['116','63','45','126'],
				rightAnswer:0
			},
			{
				question:'46 + 89 = __?',
				answers:['135','133','120','107'],
				rightAnswer:0
			},
			{
				question:'75 - 25 = __?',
				answers:['60','50','40','25'],
				rightAnswer:1
			},
			{
				question:'20 * 3 = __?',
				answers:['100','50','60','40'],
				rightAnswer:2
			},
			{
				question:'30 / 3 = __?',
				answers:['13','3','23','10'],
				rightAnswer:3
			},
			{
				question:'56 + 22 = __?',
				answers:['78','23','12','67'],
				rightAnswer:0
			}
		]
	},
	{
		id:2,
		status:'published',
		name:'Mathematics Quiz #2',
		category: 'mathematics',
		author: 'Jane Doe',
		authorUsername: 'janedoe',
		description: 'A quiz to show your basic mathematics skills.',
		scores: [],
		averageScore: null,
		bestScoreBy: [],
		bestScore: null,
		createdOn: '07/01/2019 - 12:00',
		lastModification: '07/01/2019 - 12:01',
		questions:[
			{
				question:'375 + 223 = __?',
				answers:['598','654','722','459'],
				rightAnswer:0
			},
			{
				question:'200 - 25 = __?',
				answers:['233','175','212','150'],
				rightAnswer:1
			},
			{
				question:'100 * 3 = __?',
				answers:['333','200','300','150'],
				rightAnswer:2
			},
			{
				question:'200 / 2 = __?',
				answers:['175','150','75','100'],
				rightAnswer:3
			},
			{
				question:'234 + 123 = __?',
				answers:['357','543','325','456'],
				rightAnswer:0
			},
			{
				question:'765 + 345 = __?',
				answers:['1110','1010','1222','1210'],
				rightAnswer:0
			},
			{
				question:'300 - 25 = __?',
				answers:['452','275','120','167'],
				rightAnswer:1
			},
			{
				question:'100 * 4 = __?',
				answers:['1020','300','400','250'],
				rightAnswer:2
			},
			{
				question:'600 / 2 = __?',
				answers:['275','150','200','300'],
				rightAnswer:3
			},
			{
				question:'123 + 321 = __?',
				answers:['444','333','456','654'],
				rightAnswer:0
			}

		]
	},
	{
		id:3,
		status:'published',
		name:'Mathematics Quiz #3',
		category: 'mathematics',
		author: 'Jhon Doe',
		authorUsername: 'jhondoe',
		description: 'A quiz to show your basic mathematics skills.',
		scores: [],
		averageScore: null,
		bestScoreBy: [],
		bestScore: null,
		createdOn: '07/01/2019 - 12:00',
		lastModification: '07/01/2019 - 12:01',
		questions:[
			{
				question:'1543 + 4532 = __?',
				answers:['6075','7345','3276','6109'],
				rightAnswer:0
			},
			{
				question:'1000 - 200 = __?',
				answers:['900','800','700','300'],
				rightAnswer:1
			},
			{
				question:'4500 * 2 = __?',
				answers:['5000','8000','9000','10000'],
				rightAnswer:2
			},
			{
				question:'9000 / 3 = __?',
				answers:['30000','500','2000','3000'],
				rightAnswer:3
			},
			{
				question:'7654 + 1054 = __?',
				answers:['8708','8500','7900','6352'],
				rightAnswer:0
			},
			{
				question:'6589 + 1287 = __?',
				answers:['7876','6754','8745','6123'],
				rightAnswer:0
			},
			{
				question:'2000 - 300 = __?',
				answers:['1000','1700','1600','333'],
				rightAnswer:1
			},
			{
				question:'5000 * 3 = __?',
				answers:['4000','7000','15000','20000'],
				rightAnswer:2
			},
			{
				question:'15000 / 3 = __?',
				answers:['10000','700','4000','5000'],
				rightAnswer:3
			},
			{
				question:'7927 + 3456 = __?',
				answers:['11383','7856','11001','10234'],
				rightAnswer:0
			}
		]
	},
	{
		id:4,
		status:'published',
		name:'History Quiz #1',
		category: 'history',
		author: 'Jane Doe',
		authorUsername: 'janedoe',
		description: 'A quiz about history facts.',
		scores: [],
		averageScore: null,
		bestScoreBy: [],
		bestScore: null,
		createdOn: '07/01/2019 - 12:00',
		lastModification: '07/01/2019 - 12:01',
		questions:[
			{
				question:'Approximately, when Plato was born?',
				answers:['428/427 or 424/423 BC','528/427 or 524/423 BC','328/427 or 424/323 BC','110/112 or 120/122 AC'],
				rightAnswer:0
			},
			{
				question:'Where Plato was born?',
				answers:['Corinto','Athens','Tebas','Argos'],
				rightAnswer:1
			},
			{
				question:'Approximately, when Socrates was born?',
				answers:['270 BC','370 BC','470 BC','570 BC'],
				rightAnswer:2
			},
			{
				question:'Where Socrates was born?',
				answers:['Corinto','Tebas','Argos','Athens'],
				rightAnswer:3
			},
			{
				question:'Approximately, when Socrates died?',
				answers:['399 BC','398 BC','377 BC','410 BC'],
				rightAnswer:0
			},
			{
				question:'Approximately, when Aristotle was born?',
				answers:['384–322 BC','284–222 BC','484–422 BC','584–522 BC'],
				rightAnswer:0
			},
			{
				question:'Where Aristotle was born?',
				answers:['Tebas','Stagira','Corinto','Argos'],
				rightAnswer:1
			},
			{
				question:'Approximately, when Pythagoras was born?',
				answers:['470–395 BC','670–595 BC','570–495 BC','770–695 BC'],
				rightAnswer:2
			},
			{
				question:'Where Pythagoras was born?',
				answers:['Corinto','Argos','Tebas','Samos'],
				rightAnswer:3
			},
			{
				question:'Approximately, when Pythagoras died?',
				answers:['495 BC','595 BC','695 BC','795 BC'],
				rightAnswer:0
			}
		]
	},
	{
		id:5,
		status:'published',
		name:'History Quiz #2',
		category: 'history',
		author: 'Jhon Doe',
		authorUsername: 'jhondoe',
		description: 'A quiz about history facts.',
		scores: [],
		averageScore: null,
		bestScoreBy: [],
		bestScore: null,
		createdOn: '07/01/2019 - 12:00',
		lastModification: '07/01/2019 - 12:01',
		questions:[
			{
				question:'When Michelangelo was born?',
				answers:['6 March 1475','5 May 1475','6 March 1575','4 March 1455'],
				rightAnswer:0
			},
			{
				question:'Where Michelangelo was born?',
				answers:['Rome','Caprese','Florence','Venice'],
				rightAnswer:1
			},
			{
				question:'Approximately, when Leonardo da Vinci was born?',
				answers:['14/15 April 1562','14/15 May 1452','14/15 April 1452','14/15 April 1552'],
				rightAnswer:2
			},
			{
				question:'Where Leonardo da Vinci was born?',
				answers:['Rome','Caprese','Venice','Florence'],
				rightAnswer:3
			},
			{
				question:'When Leonardo da Vinci died?',
				answers:['2 May 1519','2 May 1529','2 May 1539','10 May 1519'],
				rightAnswer:0
			},
			{
				question:'When Raphael was born?',
				answers:['March 28 or April 6, 1483','March 28 or April 6, 1487','January 28 or June 6, 1483','November 28 or December 6, 1483'],
				rightAnswer:0
			},
			{
				question:'Where Raphael was born?',
				answers:['Florence','Urbino','Rome','Venice'],
				rightAnswer:1
			},
			{
				question:'Approximately, when Donatello was born?',
				answers:['1380','1486','1386','1586'],
				rightAnswer:2
			},
			{
				question:'Where Donatello was born?',
				answers:['Rome','Caprese','Venice','Florence'],
				rightAnswer:3
			},
			{
				question:'When Donatello died?',
				answers:['13 December 1466','13 November 1466','24 December 1466','13 December 1477'],
				rightAnswer:0
			}
		]
	},
	{
		id:6,
		status:'published',
		name:'History Quiz #3',
		category: 'history',
		author: 'Jane Doe',
		authorUsername: 'janedoe',
		description: 'A quiz about history facts.',
		scores: [],
		averageScore: null,
		bestScoreBy: [],
		bestScore: null,
		createdOn: '07/01/2019 - 12:00',
		lastModification: '07/01/2019 - 12:01',
		questions:[
			{
				question:'When Picasso was born?',
				answers:['25 October 1881','20 October 1881','25 May 1881','25 October 1875'],
				rightAnswer:0
			},
			{
				question:'Where Picasso was born?',
				answers:['Madrid','Málaga','Valencia','Barcelona'],
				rightAnswer:1
			},
			{
				question:'When Dalí was born?',
				answers:['12 May 1904','11 July 1904','11 May 1904','11 May 1905'],
				rightAnswer:2
			},
			{
				question:'Where Dalí was born?',
				answers:['Rome','Caprese','Venice','Catalonia'],
				rightAnswer:3
			},
			{
				question:'When Dalí died?',
				answers:['23 January 1989','22 January 1989','23 May 1989','23 January 1999'],
				rightAnswer:0
			},
			{
				question:'When Miró was born?',
				answers:['20 April 1893','22 April 1893','20 May 1893','20 April 1899'],
				rightAnswer:0
			},
			{
				question:'Where Miró was born?',
				answers:['Madrid','Barcelona','Valencia','Málaga'],
				rightAnswer:1
			},
			{
				question:'When Vincent van Gogh was born?',
				answers:['30 May 1853','30 July 1853','30 March 1853','30 June 1853'],
				rightAnswer:2
			},
			{
				question:'Where Vincent van Gogh born?',
				answers:['La Haya','Róterdam','Zundert','Ámsterdam'],
				rightAnswer:3
			},
			{
				question:'When Vincent van Gogh died?',
				answers:['29 July 1890','29 July 1892','29 July 1894','29 May 1890'],
				rightAnswer:0
			}
		]
	}
];